Curses last forever.
Open Graves is a horror, thriller film directed by Álvaro de Armiñán.
One day, Jason finds an unusual board game called Mamba.
When his surfer friends start to play, the games unleashes its
deadly curse, killing the losers in a gruesome fashion.
Supposedly it will grant the winner a wish.
As his companions die off, Jason decides that the only way he
can reverse the tragedy is by continuing to play.
With his girlfriend, Erica, Jason rolls the dice and hopes to make
his wish before one of them suffers a horrible fate.
Jason, played by Mike Vogel.
Erica, played by Eliza Dushku.
Tomàs, played by Ethan Rains.
Elena, played by Naike Rivelli.
Lisa, played by Lindsay Caroline Robba.
Detective Izar, played by Gary Piquer.
Open Graves is a 2009 horror film directed by Álvaro
de Armiñán and written by Bruce A.
Taylor and Roderick Taylor.
The film stars Eliza Dushku, Mike Vogel, Naike Rivelli, and Lindsay Robba.
The film explores themes of witch, surfing, board game.
The tone is dark and intense.